

#### HARD SKILLS

PHP
MVC
MYSQL
LARAVEL
HTML
CSS
ANGULAR
JAVASCRIPT
GITHUB
VS CODE
SAGE BOB 50

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

Team player Communication Creative spirit LActive learning

#### LANGUAGES

French-native English-proficient Luxembourgish-beginner

## **ACTIVITIES**

Brazilian JIU-JITSU(Black Belt) Instructor & Competitor Music Travel

## INFOS

e-mail: aitisham@gmail.com tél:+352 691443222 Nationality: FRENCH Driver's licence B @github.com/isham-it @linkedin.com/in/hichamait-lachgar

# HICHAM AIT LACHGAR

## <>JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER</>

## MY BACKGROUND

After years in the food industry, I decided to change my professional career following the evolution of the digital world. I have a good sense of priorities, also experience in team management, I have ambition and I am driven by results. I have a great desire to learn and succeed in the web development sector in order to invest myself with passion.

### **EDUCATION**

WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP "CODING JOB"

BY NUMERICALL, BELVAL, LUXEMBOURG
MAY 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2021
BOOTCAMP INTENSIVE TRAINING "CODING JOBS" OF 490 HOURS OVER 5
MONTHS. DEVELOP THE MOST-VALUED TECH SKILLS OF FRONT-END AND BACK-END. GAIN EXPERTISE IN FRAMEWORKS SUCH AS ANGULAR FOR FRONT-END
AND LARAVEL, MVC, MYSQL FOR BACK-END.

TRAINING PROGRAM "CODE START"

BY NUMERICALL, WALFERDANGE, LUXEMBOURG MARCH 2021 (2 WEEKS)
LEARN HOW TO CREATE A HTML&CSS SIMPLE WEBSITE.
LEARN THE BASICS OF JAVASCRIPT LANGUAGE.

• ACCOUTING TRAINING 'HELP ACCOUNTANT'

LUXEMBOURG LIFELONG LEARNING CENTER SEPTEMBER 2018 - JANUARY 2021

• BACCALAUREATE ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING
1997

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **FOOD STORE & RETAIL MANAGER**

- KAEMPFF-KOHLER (LUXEMBOURG) MARCH 2011-FEBRUARY 2021
   Train and manage a team of 5 in-store employees.
   In charge of overall store operations.
   Buyer from suppliers in Europe.
   Assist customers in all aspects of store service.
- SUSHI SHOP (PARIS) MAY 2010-DECEMBER 2010
- FROMAGERIE 31 (PARIS) NOVEMBER 2002-APRIL 2010
- BAKERY MANAGER (PARIS) AUGUST 2000-SEPTEMBER 2002
- SALESMAN (RUNGIS) OCTOBER 1997- JUNE 2000